We're seen as the organization that is the bucket for failed social policy.
ينظر إلينا على أننا منظمة تعتبر وعاء للسياسات الاجتماعية الفاشلة.
I can't define who comes to us or how long they stay.
لا أستطيع أن أعرف من سيأتي إلينا وإلى متى سيبقى.
We get the people for whom nothing else has worked,
يأتينا الأشخاص الذين لم ينفع معهم أي شيء آخر
people who have fallen through all
أشخاص سقطوا في جميع
of the other social safety nets.
الشبكات الاجتماعية الأخرى.
They can't contain them, so we must.
لا يستطيعون احتوائهم، لذا يجب علينا ذلك.
That's our job:
هذا عملنا.
contain them, control them.
احتوائهم، التحكم فيهم.
Over the years, as a prison system,
عبر السنين، كنظام سجن،
as a nation, and as a society,
كشعب، وكأمة
we've become very good at that,
أصبحنا جيدين جدًا في ذلك،
but that shouldn't make you happy.
لكن هذا لا ينبغي أن يجعلك سعيدًا.
Today we incarcerate more people per capita
اليوم نسجن نسبا أكثر من السكان
than any other country in the world.
من أي دولة أخرى في العالم.
We have more black men in prison today
لدينا اليوم في السجون من السود أكثر
than were under slavery in 1850.
ممن كانوا تحت الاستعباد سنة 1850.
We house the parents of almost three million
لدينا آباء أكثر من ثلاثة ملايين من
of our community's children,
أطفال مجتمعنا
and we've become the new asylum,
وأصبحنا الملجأ الجديد،
the largest mental health provider in this nation.
أكبر مزود للصحة النفسية في هذه الأمة.
When we lock someone up,
عندما نحجز شخصًا ما،
that is no small thing.
هذا ليس شيئًا صغيرًا.
And yet, we are called the Department of Corrections.
مع ذلك، يدعوننا بـ"إدارة التصحيح".
Today I want to talk about
اليوم أريد الحديث عن
changing the way we think about corrections.
التغيير في طريقة تفكيرنا عن التقويم
I believe, and my experience tells me,
أنا أؤمن، وخبرتي تخبرني،
that when we change the way we think,
أننا عندما نغير طريقة تفكيرنا
we create new possibilities, or futures,
نخلق احتمالات جديدة، أو مستقبلًا جديدًا
and prisons need a different future.
والسجون تحتاج إلى مستقبل مختلف.
I've spent my entire career in corrections, over 30 years.
أمضيت كل حياتي المهنية في التقويم، ما يزيد عن 30 سنة
I followed my dad into this field.
تبعت والدي في هذا المجال.
He was a Vietnam veteran. Corrections suited him.
كان جنديًا فيتناميًا، ناسبته فكرة التصحيح.
He was strong, steady, disciplined.
لقد كان قويًا وثابتًا ومنضبطًا.
I was not so much any of those things,
لم أكن أمتلك تلك الصفات بشدة
and I'm sure that worried him about me.
وأنا متأكد أن هذا أقلقه حيالي.
Eventually I decided, if I was going to end up in prison,
أخيرًا قررت أنه إذا كان سينتهي بي المطاف في السجن
I'd better end up on the right side of the bars,
فيفضل أن أكون في الطرف الصحيح من القضبان
so I thought I'd check it out,
لذا فكرت أن أتحقق من ذلك،
take a tour of the place my dad worked,
قمت بجولةٍ في المكان الذي عمل فيه والدي
the McNeil Island Penitentiary.
جزيرة ماكنيل للسجون.
Now this was the early '80s,
وهذا كان في بداية الثمانينات،
and prisons weren't quite what you see
والسجون لم تكن تمامًا ما تشاهده
on TV or in the movies.
في التلفاز أو في الافلام.
In many ways, it was worse.
بطرق عديدة، كانت أسوأ.
I walked into a cell house that was five tiers high.
مشيت بداخل مبنى السجن الذي يحتوي على خمس طبقات
There were eight men to a cell.
كان هناك 8 رجال لكل زنزانة.
there were 550 men in that living unit.
كان هناك 550 رجلًا في المجمع.
And just in case you wondered,
وفي حال كنت تتساءل
they shared one toilet in those small confines.
فهم يتشاركون بحمام واحد في تلك الحدود الصغيرة.
An officer put a key in a lockbox,
ضابط يدخل مفتاحًا في صندوق المفاتيح
and hundreds of men streamed out of their cells.
ويتوافد مئات الأشخاص خارجين من زنزاناتهم.
Hundreds of men streamed out of their cells.
يتوافد مئات الأشخاص
I walked away as fast as I could.
مشيت بعيدًا بأسرع ما أمكنني
Eventually I went back and I started as an officer there.
أخيرًا رجعت مرة اخرى وبدأت كضابط هناك.
My job was to run one of those cell blocks
عملي كان إدارة واحدة من مجموعات الخلايا هذه
and to control those hundreds of men.
والسيطرة على هؤلاء المئات من الرجال.
When I went to work at our receptions center,
عندما ذهبت للعمل في مركز الاستقبال
I could actually hear the inmates roiling from the parking lot,
استطعت سماع أصوات السجناء من موقف السيارات
shaking cell doors, yelling,
يهزون أبواب الزنزانة ويصرخون
tearing up their cells.
يخربون زنزاناتهم.
Take hundreds of volatile people and lock them up,
خذ المئات من الأشخاص المضطربين واحتجزهم،
and what you get is chaos.
وما ستحصل عليه هو الفوضى.
Contain and control — that was our job.
الاحتواء والسيطرة، هذا عملنا.
One way we learned to do this more effectively
طريقة واحدة مكنتنا من القيام بذلك على نحو أكثر فعالية
was a new type of housing unit
نوع جديد من الوحدات السكنية
called the Intensive Management Unit, IMU,
يطلق عليه الوحدة الإدارية المشددة
a modern version of a "hole."
نسخة حديثة من "الحفرة".
We put inmates in cells behind solid steel doors
نضع المساجين في زنزانات خلف أبواب صلبة
with cuff ports so we could restrain them
مع منافذ صغيرة تمكننا من السيطرة عليهم
and feed them.
وإطعامهم.
Guess what?
خمنوا ماذا حصل؟
It got quieter.
أصبح المكان أكثر هدوء.
Disturbances died down in the general population.
الشغب قل جدًا عند عامة المساجين.
Places became safer
أصبح المكان أكثر أمانًا
because those inmates who were most violent or disruptive
لأن هؤلاء المساجين الأكثر عنفًا وشغبًا
could now be isolated.
أصبحوا الآن معزولين.
But isolation isn't good.
لكن العزل ليس جيدًا.
Deprive people of social contact and they deteriorate.
احرم الناس من التواصل الاجتماعي وسوف تتدهور حالتهم.
It was hard getting them out of IMU,
أصبح من الصعب إخراجهم من الوحدات المشددة
for them and for us.
بالنسبة لهم ولنا.
Even in prison, it's no small thing
حتى في السجن، هذا ليس شيئًا صغيرًا
to lock someone up.
أن تحتجز شخصاَ ما.
My next assignment was to one of the state's deep-end prisons
مهمتي التالية كانت في أحد أخطر سجون الولاية
where some of our more violent or disruptive inmates are housed.
حيث يحتجز أكثر الأشخاص خطرًا وعنفًا.
By then, the industry had advanced a lot,
في ذلك الوقت، تقدمت الصناعة كثيرًا
and we had different tools and techniques
وكنا نملك أدوات وطرقًا مختلفةً
to manage disruptive behavior.
للسيطرة على السلوك المضطرب.
We had beanbag guns and pepper spray
كنا نملك مسدسات المطاط ورذاذ الفلفل
and plexiglass shields,
بالإضافة إلى الدروع الزجاجية،
flash bangs, emergency response teams.
قنابل فلاشية، فريق طوارئ
We met violence with force
قمعنا الشغب بالقوة
and chaos with chaos.
والفوضى بالفوضى
We were pretty good at putting out fires.
وكنا متميزين في إخماد العنف
While I was there, I met two experienced correctional workers
عندما كنت هناك، التقيت باثنين من خبراء العمل الإصلاحي
who were also researchers,
وكانوا أيضًا باحثين،
an anthropologist and a sociologist.
مختصين بعلم الإنسان وعلم الاجتماع
One day, one of them commented to me and said,
في أحد الأيام تحدث إلي أحدهم وقال:
"You know, you're pretty good at putting out fires.
"أنت متميزً في إيقاف الشغب.
Have you ever thought about how to prevent them?"
هل فكرت يومًا كيف يمكنك منع حدوثه؟"
I was patient with them,
كنت صبورًا معهم،
explaining our brute force approach
شارحًا لهم سياستنا في استخدام القوة
to making prisons safer.
لجعل السجن أكثر أمانًا.
They were patient with me.
كانوا صبورين معي.
Out of those conversations grew some new ideas
كنتيجة لتلك المحادثات تولدت أفكار جديدة
and we started some small experiments.
وبدأنا بعض التجارب الصغيرة.
First, we started training our officers in teams
أولًا: بدأنا تدريب الضباط في مجموعات
rather than sending them one or two at a time to the state training academy.
بدلًا من إرسال كل شخص أو شخصين منهم بشكل منفرد لأكاديمية تدريب الولاية.
Instead of four weeks of training, we gave them 10.
وبدلًا من 4 ساعات تدريب في الأسبوع منحناهم 10 ساعات.
Then we experimented with an apprenticeship model
بعدها جربنا نموذج التلمذة
where we paired new staff with veteran staff.
حيث فُرز الموظفين الجدد مع الموظفين القدامى.
They both got better at the work.
تحسن أداء كليهما في العمل.
Second, we added verbal de-escalation skills
ثانيًا: أضفنا المهارات اللفظية
into the training continuum
للتدريب المتواصل
and made it part of the use of force continuum.
وجعلناه جزء من استخدام القوة المتواصل.
It was the non-force use of force.
لقد كان الاستعمال السلمي للقوة.
And then we did something even more radical.
ثم قمنا بشيءٍ أكثر تطرفًا.
We trained the inmates on those same skills.
دربنا المساجين على هذه المهارات.
We changed the skill set,
غيرنا مجموعة المهارات
reducing violence, not just responding to it.
عدم الاكتفاء بالاستجابة للعنف، بل الحد منه.
Third, when we expanded our facility, we tried a new type of design.
ثالثًا: عندما وسعنا منشأتنا جربنا نوعًا جديدًا من التصاميم.
Now the biggest and most controversial component
أصبحت الآن أكبر وأكثر العناصر المثيرة للجدل
of this design, of course, was the toilet.
بالنسبة للتصميم، طبعًا دورات المياه.
There were no toilets.
لم يكن هناك دورات مياه.
Now that might not sound significant to you here today,
قد لا يبدو هذا الأمر مهمًا لكم هنا اليوم
but at the time, it was huge.
لكن في ذلك الوقت، كان أمرًا عظيمًا.
No one had ever heard of a cell without a toilet.
لم يسمع أحد من قبل بزنزانة من دون مرحاض.
We all thought it was dangerous and crazy.
ظننا جميعًا أنه أمرٌ خطيرٌ ومجنون.
Even eight men to a cell had a toilet.
حتى الزنزانة التي تحتوي 8 أشخاص تحتوي مرحاضًا.
That small detail changed the way we worked.
هذا التغيير الصغير غير طريقة عملنا.
Inmates and staff started interacting
بدأ المساجين والموظفون بالتفاعل
more often and openly and developing a rapport.
بشكل أكبر وأكثر انفتاحًا وبدأت تنشأ علاقات.
It was easier to detect conflict and intervene
سَهَّل ذلك عملية كشف الصراعات والتدخل
before it escalated.
قبل أن تتصاعد.
The unit was cleaner, quieter, safer and more humane.
أصبحت الوحدة أكثر نظافة وهدوء وإنسانية.
This was more effective at keeping the peace
كانت هذه الطريقة أكثر فاعلية في الحفاظ على السلام
than any intimidation technique I'd seen to that point.
من أي أسلوب ترهيبي رأيته حتى تلك اللحظة.
Interacting changes the way you behave,
التفاعل يغير سلوكك
both for the officer and the inmate.
سواءً كنت ضابطًا أو مسجونًا.
We changed the environment and we changed the behavior.
غيرنا البيئة وغيرنا السلوك.
Now, just in case I hadn't learned this lesson,
الآن، في حال لم أتعلم الدرس جيدًا
they assigned me to headquarters next,
قاموا بتعييني في المقر الرئيسي
and that's where I ran straight up against system change.
وهناك سعيت بشكل حثيث ضد تغيير النظام.
Now, many things work against system change:
هناك أشياء كثيرة تسعى ضد تغيير النظام:
politics and politicians, bills and laws,
السياسة والسياسيون والفواتير والقوانين
courts and lawsuits, internal politics.
المحاكم والدعاوى القضائية والسياسة الداخلية.
System change is difficult and slow,
تغيير النظام صعب وبطيء
and oftentimes it doesn't take you
وفي كثير من الأحيان لا يؤدي
where you want to go.
إلى ما تتوقعه منه.
It's no small thing to change a prison system.
ليس شيئًا سهلًا أن تغير نظام سجن
So what I did do is I reflected on my earlier experiences
إذا ما فعلته هو انعكاس لتجربتي السابقة
and I remembered that when we interacted with offenders, the heat went down.
وأتذكر عندما تفاعلنا مع المخالفين، تضاءلت نسبة العنف
When we changed the environment, the behavior changed.
عندما غيرنا البيئة تغير السلوك
And these were not huge system changes.
وهذه لم تكن تغييرات ضحمة في النظام
These were small changes, and these changes
لقد كانت تغييرات بسيطة، وهذه التغييرات
created new possibilities.
خلقت احتمالات جديدة
So next, I got reassigned as superintendent of a small prison.
إذا بعد ذلك، تم تعييني كمشرف على سجن صغير
And at the same time, I was working on my degree
وفي نفس الوقت، لقد كنت أعمل على شهادتي
at the Evergreen State College.
من كلية إيفرغرين الحكومية
I interacted with a lot of people who were not like me,
تفاعلت مع العديد من الأشخاص الذين لم يكونوا مثلي.
people who had different ideas
أشخاص يمتلكون أفكارًا مختلفة
and came from different backgrounds.
وجاءوا من خلفيات فكرية مختلفة
One of them was a rainforest ecologist.
أحدهم كانت عالمة بيئة
She looked at my small prison and what she saw
هي رأت سجني الصغير وكل ما رأته
was a laboratory.
هو مختبر
We talked and discovered how prisons and inmates
تناقشنا واكتشفنا كيف أن السجن والمساجين
could actually help advance science
يستطيع أن يساعدو في العلوم المتقدمة
by helping them complete projects
عبر مساعدتهم بإكمال مشروعات
they couldn't complete on their own,
لم يستطيعوا إكمالها لوحدهم
like repopulating endangered species:
مثل الاعتناء بالكائنات المهددة بالانقراض
frogs, butterflies, endangered prairie plants.
ضفادع، فراشات، نباتات مهددة بالانقراض
At the same time, we found ways to make
وفي نفس الوقت، وجدنا طريقة لجعل
our operation more efficient
عمليتنا أكثر فعالية
through the addition of solar power,
عبر إضافة الطاقة الشمسية
rainwater catchment, organic gardening, recycling.
مجمع لمياه الامطار، حدائق طبيعية، إعادة تدوير
This initiative has led to many projects
المبادرة قادتنا للعديد من المشروعات
that have had huge system-wide impact,
التي تملك تغيير عظيم في المنظومة
not just in our system, but in other state systems as well,
ليس فقط في نظامنا، بل في الأنظمة الأخرى أيضًا
small experiments making a big difference
تجربة صغيرة أحدثت تغيير كبير
to science, to the community.
للعلم، وللبشرية
The way we think about our work changes our work.
الطريقة التي نفكر بها عن عملنا تغير عملنا
The project just made my job more interesting and exciting.
المشروع جعل عملي أكثر متعة وأكثر حماسًا
I was excited. Staff were excited.
كنت متحمسًا، الموظفين كانوا متحمسين
Officers were excited. Inmates were excited.
الضباط كانوا متحمسين، المساجين كانوا متحمسين
They were inspired.
لقد كانوا ملهمين
Everybody wanted to be part of this.
كل شخص يريد أن يكون جزء من هذا
They were making a contribution, a difference,
لقد قدموا مساهمة، تغيير،
one they thought was meaningful and important.
مساهمة اعتقدوا أنها معبرة ومهمة
Let me be clear on what's going on here, though.
دعوني أكن واضحًا عما يحدث هنا، على الرغم ان
Inmates are highly adaptive.
المساجين لديهم قدرة عالية على التكيف
They have to be.
يجب عليهم ذلك.
Oftentimes, they know more about our own systems
دائمًا، هم يعرفون عن نظامنا أكثر
than the people who run them.
من الأشخاص الذين يديرونهم
And they're here for a reason.
وهما هنا لسبب
I don't see my job as to punish them or forgive them,
لا أرى عملي معاقبتهم أو مسامحتهم،
but I do think they can have
لكن أعتقد أنهم يستحقون
decent and meaningful lives even in prison.
حياة كريمة وذات معنى حتى في السجن
So that was the question:
إذًا هذا هو السؤال:
Could inmates live decent and meaningful lives,
هل يمكن للمساجين أن يعيشو حياة كريمة وذات معنى،
and if so, what difference would that make?
وإذا أمكنهم، ما التغيير الذي سيحدثه ذلك؟
So I took that question back to the deep end,
إذا اخذت السؤال مرة اخرى لنهاية عميقة،
where some of our most violent offenders are housed.
حيث يتواجد أكثر المجرمين عنفًا
Remember, IMUs are for punishment.
تذكر، الوحدة المشددة وضعت للعقاب
You don't get perks there, like programming.
لا تحصل على امتيازات هناك، مثل التأهيل
That was how we thought.
هذا كان تفكيرنا سابقًا
But then we started to realize that if any inmates
لكن عندما بدأنا باستنتاج أن أي سجين
needed programming, it was these particular inmates.
يحتاج للبرمجة، لقد كانوا سجناء محدودين
In fact, they needed intensive programming.
في الحقيقة، هم يحتاجون برمجة مكثفة
So we changed our thinking 180 degrees,
إذا غيرنا طريقة تفكيرنا بصورة مختلفة تمامًا
and we started looking for new possibilities.
وبدأنا بالبحث عن احتمالات جديدة
What we found was a new kind of chair.
وما وجدنا هو نوع جديد من الكراسي
Instead of using the chair for punishment,
بدلا من استخدام كرسي العقاب
we put it in classrooms.
وضعناه على شكل صفوف
Okay, we didn't forget our responsibility to control,
حسنًا، لم ننسى مسؤوليتنا في المراقبة
but now inmates could interact safely, face-to-face
لكن الآن السجناء يمكنهم التفاعل بأمان، وجهًا لوجه
with other inmates and staff,
مع المساجين الآخرين والموظفين،
and because control was no longer an issue,
ولأن السيطرة لم تكن بعد الآن مشكلة
everybody could focus on other things,
كل شخص يمكن أن يركز على أشياء أخرى
like learning. Behavior changed.
مثل التعلم، تغيير السلوك
We changed our thinking, and we changed what was possible, and this gives me hope.
غيرنا تفكيرنا وغيرنا الاحتمالات، وهذا يعطي الأمل
Now, I can't tell you that any of this stuff will work.
الآن، لا أستطيع أن أخبركم أن أيا من هذه الأشياء سينجح
What I can tell you, though, it is working.
ما أستطيع أن أخبركم به، أنه ناجح
Our prisons are getting safer for both staff and inmates,
سجننا أصبح أكثر امانًا للموظفين والمساجين
and when our prisons are safe,
وإذا كان السجن آمنًا،
we can put our energies into a lot more than just controlling.
نستطيع أن نضع طاقاتنا في أشياء أكبر بكثير من المراقبة والسيطرة
Reducing recidivism may be our ultimate goal,
تقليل نسبة الانتكاس ربما هو هدفنا النهائي.
but it's not our only goal.
ولكن ليس الوحيد
To be honest with you, preventing crime
لأكون صادقًا معكم، منع الجريمة
takes so much more from so many more people
تأخذ أكثر بكثير من أشخاص عديدين
and institutions.
وإصلاحيات.
If we rely on just prisons to reduce crime,
إذا اعتمدنا فقط على السجون للحد من الجريمة،
I'm afraid we'll never get there.
أنا أخشى أنني لن نصل هناك.
But prisons can do some things
لكن السجون تستطيع فعل بعض الأشياء
we never thought they could do.
لم نتوقع أنها تستطيع فعلها
Prisons can be the source of innovation
السجون تستطيع أن تكون مصدرًا للاختراعات
and sustainability,
والاستمرارية.
repopulating endangered species and environmental restoration.
العناية بالمخلوقات المهددة بالانقراض وإصلاح البيئة
Inmates can be scientists and beekeepers,
المساجين يستطيعون أن يكونوا علماء، نحالين
dog rescuers.
منقذين كلاب
Prisons can be the source of meaningful work
السجن يمكن أن يكون مصدر لحياة ذات معنى
and opportunity for staff
وفرصًا للموظفين،
and the inmates who live there.
والمساجين الذين يعيشون فيه.
We can contain and control
نستطيع أن نحتوي وأن نسيطر
and provide humane environments.
وأن نوفر بيئة انسانية
These are not opposing qualities.
وهذه ليست خصائص متعارضة
We can't wait 10 to 20 years to find out
نستطيع الانتظار 10 و20 سنة لاكتشاف ذلك
if this is worth doing.
إذا كان هذا يستحق العمل عليه.
Our strategy is not massive system change.
استراتيجيتنا ليست تغيير عظيم في النظام
Our strategy is hundreds of small changes
استراتيجيتنا عبارة عن مئات من التغييرات الطفيفة
that take place in days or months, not years.
التي يمكن تطبيقها في يوم وشهر، وليست سنوات
We need more small pilots where we learn as we go,
نحتاج مرشدين صغار حيث نتعلم ونحن نمضي
pilots that change the range of possibility.
مرشدين يغيرون نطاق الاحتمالات
We need new and better ways to measure impacts
نحتاج طرق جديدة ومميزة لقياس مدى التأثير
on engagement, on interaction,
في المشاركة، التفاعل
on safe environments.
في البيئة الآمنة
We need more opportunities to participate in
نحتاج فرص جديدة للمشاركة فيها
and contribute to our communities,
ومساهمات لصالح مجتمعاتنا،
your communities.
مجتمعاتكم،
Prisons need to be secure, yes, safe, yes.
السجن تحتاج أن تكون آمنة، نعم آمنة
We can do that.
نستطيع أن نفعل ذلك.
Prisons need to provide humane environments
السجون بحاجة لأن تكون بيئة انسانية
where people can participate, contribute,
حيث باستطاعة الناس المشاركة، المساهمة
and learn meaningful lives.
وتعلم حياة ذات مغزى.
We're learning how to do that.
نحن نتعلم كيف نفعل ذلك.
That's why I'm hopeful.
وهذا ما يجعلني متفائلًا
We don't have to stay stuck in old ideas about prison.
لسنا بحاجة لأن نبقى عالقين بأفكار قديمة عن السجن
We can define that. We can create that.
نستطيع تعريف ذلك. نستطيع خلق ذلك
And when we do that thoughtfully and with humanity,
وعندما نفعل ذلك بشكل مدروس وإنساني
prisons can be more than the bucket
السجون تستطيع أن تكون أكثر من وعاء
for failed social policy.
لفشل في السياسة الاجتماعية
Maybe finally, we will earn our title:
وربما أخيرًا. نستطيع أن نكتسب باستحقاق لقبنا
a department of corrections.
قسم التصحيحات
Thank you.
شكرًا لكم.